Zoë Melisko

UX/UI DESIGNER + FRONT-END DEVELOPER

www.zoemelisko.com

linkedin.com/in/zoëmelisko

zoe@zoemelisko.com

(818) 631-5808

SKILLS

Design

Wireframing

Prototyping

Persona + Scenarios

Design Strategy

Design Studios

Mobile Design

Responsive Web Design

Research

User Interviews

Usability Testing

Field study

Contextual Inquiry

Affinity Mapping

Flow + Site Diagrams

Task Analysis

Tools

Sketch

Asana

InVision

Framer JS

Photoshop

Axure

Balsamiq

Adobe Suite Marvel

Principle

Programming

HTML + CSS jQuery

JavaScript

React

EDUCATION

General Assembly

UX Design Immersive
Front-End Web Development
Javascript Development

Moorpark College

SUMMARY

I'm a UX/UI Designer with a knack for Front-End Development. My combined skill set and curiosity of human behavior allow me to understand, design, and build user experiences collaboratively across teams to help bring ideas into a reality. My core strength as a designer lies in conducting **thorough user research**, **building high quality annotated user flows**, **wireframing of various fidelities**, and **interactive prototypes** for establishing and justifying the product direction.

EXPERIENCE

Worklab.io | Front-End Developer (Contract)

Dec 2019 - Present

A tech development agency seeking front-end development help across various client projects.

- Coded PDF templates
- Built custom Wordpress site utilizing the Divi theming framework

Concierge | UX/UI Designer (Contract)

Nov 2019 - Present

A transportation logistics company in the process of rebranding looking for a functional and responsive redesign of their website.

- Helped stakeholder pinpoint key user demographics and unique value proposition within the travel tech marketplace.
- Spearheaded user interface design including typography and moodboarding selections for stakeholder.

TRKX | UI Designer + Front-End Developer (Contract)

Aug 2019 - Nov 2019

A worldwide transport and logistics service provider wanting to apply new branding to a custom user facing website.

- Worked directly with stakeholders in collaborative design studios.
- Presented design mock-ups for stakeholders to ensure quality control and satisfaction before project development phase.
- Developed responsive user interface using HTML/SCSS, React components, and jQuery.

Choisi | UX Designer

Dec 2018 - Jan 2019

A luxury fashion site seeking to implement personalization features and eCommerce functionality to complement their innovative AI technology.

- Conducted user and industry research including user interviews, usability testing, A/B testing, heuristic evaluation, competitive analysis, and affinity mapping.
- Collaborated directly with company co-founder in design studios to establish design layout, feature implementation, and ensure brand consistency.
- Lead the creation of personalization features including Shop the Look, Editors Picks, and user testimonials to encourage browsing & purchases.